
    [
        {
            "id": "1",
            "question":"Earth moving around the sun at  ____________ per hour",
            "answers": ["670,000 miles","67,000 miles", "6,700 miles", "670 miles"],
            "correctAnswer": "67,000 miles"

        },
        {
            "id": "2",
            "question":"Earth is Mostly Comprised of the following except ________",
            "answers": ["Iron", "Air", "Silicon", "Oxygen"],
            "correctAnswer": "Air"

        },
        {
            "id": "3",
            "question":"The highest recorded temperature on Earth is  ________",
            "answers": ["134 degrees Fahrenheit", "34 degrees Fahrenheit", "20 degrees Fahrenheit", "160 degrees Fahrenheit"],
            "correctAnswer": "134 degrees Fahrenheit"

        },
        {
            "id": "4",
            "question":"It takes the Earth exactly how long to rotate on its axis?",
            "incorrectAnswers": ["24 hours", "23 hours, 56 minutes and 4 seconds", "24 minutes", "23 days, 56 hours and 4 minutes"],
            "correctAnswer": "23 hours, 56 minutes and 4 seconds"

        },
        {
            "id": "5",
            "question":"Earth is 4.5 Billion Years Old",
            "incorrectAnswers": ["True", "False"],
            "correctAnswer": "True"

        },
        {
            "id": "6",
            "question":"The lowest recorded temperature on Earth is _______",
            "incorrectAnswers": ["128.5 degrees Fahrenheit", "0 degrees Fahrenheit", "-100.5 degrees Fahrenheit","-128.5 degrees Fahrenheit"],
            "correctAnswer": "-128.5 degrees Fahrenheit"

        },
        {
            "id": "7",
            "question":"The Earthâ€™s Atmosphere Extends to a Distance of 10,000 km",
            "incorrectAnswers": ["False", "True", "Maybe"],
            "correctAnswer": "True"

        },
        {
            "id": "8",
            "question":"A year on Earth is exactly ______ days ",
            "incorrectAnswers": ["366", "365", "365.2564", "300"],
            "correctAnswer": "365.2564"

        },
        {
            "id": "9",
            "question":"",
            "incorrectAnswers": ["nearly 30 kilometers per second", "nearly 30 meters per second", "nearly 30 kilometers per minute", "nearly 30 meters per minute"],
            "correctAnswer": "nearly 30 kilometers per second"

        },
        {
            "id": "10",
            "question":"Earth is Almost a Sphere",
            "incorrectAnswers": ["True", "False", "I don't know"],
            "correctAnswer": "True"

        }
    ]
